const bibleQuestions = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: "The Bible is the most popular book ever written(by copies sold). True or False?",
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is the first book in the Bible?",
        answer: "Genesis"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "How many days did God take to create the world?",
        answer: "6"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Who were Adam and Eve's three sons listed in the Bible?",
        answer: "Cain, Abel, Seth"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Who did God tell to build an ark?",
        answer: "Noah"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "What did Jacob give Joseph that sparked jealousy from his siblings?",
        answer: "A coat of many colours"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "How did Moses' mother save him from the Egyptian soldiers?",
        answer: "Put him in a basket in the river"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Through what did God speak to Moses in the desert?",
        answer: "A burning bush"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "What did Moses say God commanded the Pharaoh to do?",
        answer: " Let his people go"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "How many plagues did God send on Egypt?",
        answer: "10"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What was the final plague that convinced Pharaoh to let the slaves go?",
        answer: "The firstborn son of all Egyptian families died"
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "When Pharaoh changed his mind and sent his army after the slaves, where did they meet at?",
        answer: "By the Red Sea"
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "What did God through Moses to save the slaves?",
        answer: "Parted the Red Sea."
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: "When the Egyptians tried to follow the Israelites through the Red Sea, what happened?",
        answer: "The water crashed on them and killed them all"
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: "Where did God give Moses the Ten Commandments?",
        answer: "Mt. Sinai"
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: "What golden image did the Israelites make at Mt. Sinai?",
        answer: "A golden calf"
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: "Who was the first king of Israel?",
        answer: "Saul"
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: "When Daniel prayed to God after it was not allowed, where was he thrown into?",
        answer: "The lion's den"
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question: "Who was Jesus' human mother?",
        answer: "Mary"
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: "Who was Jesus' adoptive father on Earth?",
        answer: "Joseph"
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question: "Who was Jesusâ€™ birth father?",
        answer: "God"
    },
]

export { bibleQuestions }